HÅKAN NILSSON

UX DESIGNER

Portfolio: hnilssonportfolio.com

h.n.j.nilsson@gmail.com
Mondragón, Spain
+34 677 89 43 01

linkedin.com/in/håkan-nilsson-8aaa24

_		
)
П	n	

EDUCATION

User-Centered Design and Design Thinking.

IDF / Online / 2020

Web Design and Web Programming.

University West / Online / 2016

Bachelor in Tourism Management and Economics.

Linnaeus University / Kalmar / 2012

SKILLS

Figma Photoshop InVision HTML CSS/Sass Jira User Research Wireframing Typography Colour theory

LANGUAGES

Swedish Native
English Advanced level
Spanish Advanced level
Danish Basic level
Norwegian Basic level

GLOBAL EXPERIENCES

Consolidated interpersonal and intercultural skills: strong cultural understanding and broad global view acquired by living and working in more than 60 countries.

PROFILE

UX Designer enthusiastic about delivering efficient user-centred Web and App designs. Highly skilled in the Design Thinking process and mock-up and prototyping tools. An excellent and creative team worker with strong and enriching intercultural experience.

RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

ONLINE ENGLISH TEACHER

MondragonLingua / Jul 2012 - Present / Mondragón Instructed 40-50 online weekly classes in English.

Created unique lesson plans to engage different student levels.

Assessed students' background information to determine learning strengths and weaknesses.

Tested and evaluated students on their comprehension of lesson material.

CALL CENTER CUSTOMER SUPPORT REPRESENTATIVE

eBay / Sep 2007 - Sep 2008 / Dublin

Resolved customer queries by solving them rapidly, achieving a high level of customer satisfaction.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Markaryds Grafiska / Aug 2000 - Dec 2004 / Markaryd

Developed a wide range of designs for print and provided clients with production-ready graphics in PDF-format.

Produced digital image files to be printed or used in digital printing methods.